Associated Industries of New York State / The Business Council of New York State; Records apap043
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- President's Files, 1977-1979; 3; 1.14 cubic ft.
  - Speech to the Energy Conference--Panel, 1978 September 21 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 45)
  - Speech at the Environmental Conference, 1978 September 21 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 46)
  - Speech to the Northeast Chapter of the Air Pollution Control Association, 1978 September 28 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 47)
  - Speech to Binghamton Rotary, 1978 October 3 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 48)
  - Statement on Business and Government in New York State, 1978 October 7 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 49)
  - Speech to the Westchester Builders Association, 1978 October 12 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 50)
  - Speech at General Electric's 100th Anniversary Dinner, 1978 October 13 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 51)
  - Speech to the Management Executives Conference, 1978 October 17 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 52)
  - Speech to New York Telephone Seminar, 1978 October 25 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 53)
  - Speech to Environmental Conference, 1978 November 2 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 54)
  - Speech to Sylvania Management, 1978 November 13 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 55)
  - Speech to Syracuse/Onondaga Conference, 1978 November 15 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 56)
  - Speech to the Schenectady Rotary, 1978 November 30 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 57)
  - Speech at Associated Industries' Membership Meeting, Rochester, 1978 December 12 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 58)
  - Speech at Associated Industries' Membership Meeting, Buffalo, 1978 December 12 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 59)
  - Speech at Associated Industries' Membership Meeting, Syracuse, 1978 December 13 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 60)
  - Speech to New York Telephone Seminar, 1979 February 07 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 61)
  - Speech to Oneida Management Group, 1979 February 22 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 62)
  - Speech to Associated Industries' Membership Meeting, Utica, 1979 February 22 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 63)
  - Speech to State Government Relations Committee-American Paper Institute, 1979 March 1 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 64)
  - Speech to Citizens Foundation, 1979 March 2 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 65)
  - Speech to New York Telephone Association, 1979 March 6 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 66)
  - Speech to the AFL-CIO, 1979 March 6 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 67)
  - Speech to School Boards Association, 1979 March 12 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 68)
  - Speech to Magazine Publishers Association, 1979 March 16 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 69)
  - Speech to the Southern Tier Industrial Group, 1979 March 22 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 70)
  - Speech to Union Carbide, 1979 March 26 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 71)
  - Statement on Retail Marketing Divorcement in the Petroleum Industry, 1979 April 4 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 72)
  - Speech for Harry E. Salzburg Memorial Lecture Program, 1979 April 6 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 73)
  - Speech to Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1979 April 24 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 74)
  - Speech to Niagara Falls Chamber of Commerce, 1979 May 2 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 75)
  - Speech at Boy Scout Dinner, 1979 May 4 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 76)
  - Speech to Buffalo Executives Association, 1979 May 7 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 77)
  - Speech to New York Telephone Seminar, 1979 May 9 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 78)
  - Speech to Transportation Council Meeting, 1979 May 15 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 79)
  - Moderator at Siena College Insurance Seminar, 1979 May 17 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 80)
  - Speech to the Chenango Chamber of Commerce, 1979 May 25 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 81)
  - Speech to the Arthritis Foundation, 1979 May 31 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 82)
  - Speech on Energy Advisory Service, 1979 April 25 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 83)
  - Speech to the Syracuse Rotary, 1979 June 15 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 84)
  - Statement on Tax Reductions and New York's Retail Potential, 1979 July (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 85)
  - Speech to M.A.C.N.Y. Board, 1979 July 12 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 86)
  - Speech at Associated Industries' Annual Meeting, 1979 September 21 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 87)
  - Speech to Association of Colleges and Universities, 1979 October 9 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 88)
  - Speech to Community Colleges' Trustees and Councils, 1979 October 13 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 89)
  - Speech to Association of Colleges and Universities, 1979 October 9 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 88)
  - Speech to Community Colleges' Trustees and Councils, 1979 October 13 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 89)
  - Speech to Bankers for the Expansion of New York's Economy (B.E.N.Y.E.), 1979 October 17 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 90)
  - Speech to Chemical Bank, 1979 October 24 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 91)
  - Speech to Bankers for the Expansion of New York's Economy (B.E.N.Y.E.), 1979 November 14 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 92)
  - Speech to Olean Chapter of International Management Council, 1979 November 15 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 93)
  - Speech to Albany Chapter of Financial Executives Institute, 1979 December 10 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 94)
  - Speech Before the Temporary Commission to Review Sales and Use Tax Laws, 1979 December 11 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 95)
  - Speech to Cobleskill Chamber of Commerce, 1979 December 19 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 96)
  - Memoranda to Members of the Board of Directors and the Executive Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 97)
  - Memoranda to Members of the Board of Directors and the Executive Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 4 (3-President's Files), Folder 98)
- Finance Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1925-1935; 1943-1947; 4; 0.1 cubic ft.
  Minutes are glued onto scrapbook pages.
  General minutes of the meetings of the Finance Committee.
  - Finance Committee Minutes, 1928-1935; 1943-1947 (Box 34 (4-Finance Committee, Meeting Minutes), Folder 99)
- Former Directors, Files on, 1950-1981; 5; 1 cubic foot
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Files on individual directors, containing tables of the directors' association with Associated Industries, correspondence concerning their directorships, photographs and news clippings.
  General files contain lists of members of the Board of Directors and the Executive Committee (1961-80), files for various directors' committees (1957, 1960, 1966-67, 1974-78), and versions of the constitution and by-laws of Associated Industries (1962-80).
  - Ackerman, A., 1964; 1971 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 100)
  - Baribault, Richard P., 1976 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 103)
  - Barrett, W., 1963-1973 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 104)
  - Berens, J. R., 1976-1978 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 105)
  - Boulton, Robert G., 1978-1979 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 106)
  - Callihan, John., 1977-1980 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 107)
  - Castle, John H., Jr., 1968 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 108)
  - Catherwood, Martin P., Dr., 1971; 1978 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 109)
  - Clark, J. Reid, 1977-1978; 1981 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 110)
  - Clark, Paul T., 1971; 1974-1975 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 111)
  - Concannon, Thomas J. Jr., 1981 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 112)
  - Coupe, Douglass, 1974-1975 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 113)
  - Craig, Donald E., 1970 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 114)
  - Craugh, Joseph P., 1969-1970 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 115)
  - Crowley, Francis E., 1972-1973 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 116)
  - Drake, Francis E., Jr., 1968-1981 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 117)
  - Douglas, George W., 1974-1975 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 118)
  - Else, Richard I., 1970; 1976 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 119)
  - Emery, Charles H., 1969; 1974 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 120)
  - Evans, Aubrey M., 1960; 1967; 1974-1975 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 121)
  - Evans, Edwin, 1970 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 122)
  - Evans, Harold S., 1977 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 123)
  - Flynn, Robert E., 1979-1981 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 124)
  - Fraser, A. D. Ross, 1959; 1975-1976 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 125)
  - French, Seth B., Jr., 1977; 1980 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 126)
  - Fuller, David O., Jr., 1980 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 127)
  - Gavin, Joseph G., Jr., 1978 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 128)
  - George, Charles W., 1972; 1975 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 129)
  - Geyer, Vean L., 1959; 1964; 1972 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 130)
  - Gisel, William G., 1961; 1979 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 131)
  - Gorevan, John M., 1980 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 132)
  - Granville, William H., 1972-1973; 1977 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 133)
  - Haehl, John G., 1975; 1977 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 134)
  - Hall, A. J., 1972-1973; 1977; 1980 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 135)
  - Hallauer, Carl S., 1971-1972; 1974 (Box 4 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 136)
  - Harby, Jack D., 1971-1972; 1974 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 1)
  - Harden, Frank E., 1967; 1976 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 2)
  - Henderson, James, 1975-1977 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 3)
  - Hinman, R., 1965-1966; 1973 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 4)
  - Hoffman, Alexander, 1979-1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 5)
  - Horey, Thomas A., 1976; 1980-1981 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 6)
  - Howe, Robert H., 1974-1977 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 7)
  - Hull, Gerald P., 1967-1968 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 8)
  - Hultz, Jack M., 1976; 1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 9)
  - Hustead, Thomas E., 1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 10)
  - Jasper, David W., 1970 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 12)
  - Jordan, Robert M., 1966; 1975 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 13)
  - Keylley, Royden K., 1971-1972; 1976 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 14)
  - Kennedy, Charles F., 1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 15)
  - Kilpatrick, Frank E., 1970; 1972 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 16)
  - Knight, Frederick H., 1952; 1972; 1979 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 17)
  - Knight, T. Spencer, 1972; 1976-1977 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 18)
  - Knowlton, David, 1975-1978 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 19)
  - Liptak, Thomas M., 1971-1974; 1978 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 20)
  - Lowe, E. Nobles, 1969; 1977 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 21)
  - Lynch, William L., Jr., 1972; 1979-1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 22)
  - MacAllister, John G., 1975; 1977; 1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 23)
  - MacKay, William E., 1970 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 24)
  - McCann, Thomas D., 1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 25)
  - McComb, James N., 1970; 1976 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 26)
  - McGovern, John B., 1976; 1979-1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 27)
  - McMullen, Albert J., 1967; 1981 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 28)
  - McHugh, Keith S., 1967; 1973-1975 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 29)
  - McNitt, James D., 1970 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 30)
  - Mann, Eugene T., 1977; 1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 31)
  - Metcalf, Frank, 1967; 1978; 1981 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 32)
  - Mitchell, O. J., Jr., 1972-1974 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 33)
  - Mitchell, O. J., Sr., 1968 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 34)
  - Mitchell, Robert E., 1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 35)
  - Moore, Kenneth, 1968; 1976 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 36)
  - Morris, Richard, 1971; 1977 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 37)
  - Murray, James F., 1971-1972; 1979 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 38)
  - O'Neill, James A., 1971; 1973 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 39)
  - Petersen, George W., 1976; 1979 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 40)
  - Porter, Marc E., 1967 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 41)
  - Ransom, R., 1979-1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 42)
  - Reed, Everett, 1963; 1975 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 43)
  - Relyea, J. Fred, 1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 44)
  - Rettaliata, John B., 1978 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 45)
  - Richards, H. Eugene, 1976; 1979 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 46)
  - Rippeteau, Darrel D., 1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 47)
  - Robertson, Miles E., 1972 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 48)
  - Rumrill, Charles L., 1972 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 49)
  - Sanger, Norman F., 1972-1976; 1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 50)
  - Sherran, Clifford, 1967; 1974; 1976 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 51)
  - Shepard, W. F., 1971-1972; 1981 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 52)
  - Shoemaker, Garth A., 1950; 1962; 1972; 1978 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 53)
  - Silliman, Leo R., 1969; 1973; 1976 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 54)
  - Slater, Harry G., 1970-1971 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 55)
  - Snyder, Paul L., 1970-1971 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 56)
  - Stein, Josef, 1981 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 57)
  - Stevenson, Wade, 1957; 1972 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 58)
  - Stone, Franz T., 1970; 1979 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 59)
  - Strickland, M. Carter, 1969; 1971-1972 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 60)
  - Taylor, William A., 1958; 1967; 1971-1978 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 61)
  - Timmis, James M., 1969; 1975; 1977 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 62)
  - Torrey, Richard F., 1979-1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 63)
  - Tunney, Eugene J., 1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 64)
  - Turner, Tom, 1971 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 65)
  - Vanderslice, Thomas A., 1970-1972 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 66)
  - Walsh, John M., 1976-1977 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 67)
  - Waters, Richard, 1964; 1970-1972; 1976-1977; 1981 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 68)
  - Weidlein, Edward R., 1974-1975; 1981 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 69)
  - Welch, John F., 1981 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 70)
  - Welsh, Frederic S., 1973; 1976 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 71)
  - Wiegand, Glenn W., 1973; 1980-1981 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 72)
  - Williams, John F., 1977-1979 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 73)
  - Wilson, Malcolm, 1975; 1979-1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 74)
  - Winger, Albert E., 1971 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 75)
  - Zwicker, L. A., 1964; 1972-1973 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 76)
  - Zornow, Gerald B., 1970; 1973 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 77)
  - Board of Directors, Elections and Resignations, 1965-1972 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 78)
  - Board of Directors, Policy Statements and Resolutions, 1972-1977 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 79)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1962-1980 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 80)
  - Directors' Area Meetings, 1960 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 81)
  - Directors' Committee on Compensation, 1975 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 82)
  - Directors' Committee on Constitution, 1976-1977 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 83)
  - Directors' Committee on Group Insurance, 1976 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 84)
  - Directors' Committee, Nominating, 1974-1979 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 85)
  - Directors' Committee on Nomination for Chairman, First Vice-Chairman, Second Vice-Chairman, 1957; 1966-1967 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 86)
  - Directors' Committee on Pensions, 1960; 1976-1977 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 87)
  - Directors' Committee to Review Dues Schedule and Membership Program, 1976-1978 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 88)
  - Directors' Committees, 1976-1979 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 89)
  - Directors Lists, Obsolete, 1961-1972 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 90-91)
  - Directors Lists, Miscellaneous, 1971-1981 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 92)
  - Directors' Search Committee, 1975 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 93)
  - Executive Committee, Make-Up, 1963; 1966-1977 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 94)
  - Memorandum Regarding Qualifications for Directorship, 1974 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 95)
  - Political Action Committees, Directors, 1975-1976 (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 96)
  - President's Report to the Board of Directors, 1978 July (Box 5 (5-Former Directors, Files on), Folder 97)
- Press Releases of Associated Industries, 1975-1979; 6; 0.4 cubic ft.
  Press releases and drafts of these from Associated Industries of New York, including some printed on the AINY letterhead, some titled "For the Press," some titled "Joint News Release" from AINY, the Empire State Chamber of Commerce, New York State Council of Retail Merchants, New York Chamber of Commerce and Industry, also including some written "statements" and "specials to" newspapers by Raymond T. Schuler, and a few news releases from other sources but on subjects which concerned AINY. Note: The complete text of any speech of Raymond T. Schuler's mentioned in a press release can be found filed chronologically with the speeches in the President's File.
  - Press Releases of Associated Industries, 1975 January-1976 April; 1977 January-1978 September; 1978 September-1979 January; 1979 January-1979 October (Box 5 (6-Press Releases of Associated Industries), Folder 98-103)
- Publications of Associated Industries, 1958-1966; 1976-1979; 7; 3.5 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically by title or type of publication, and arranged chronologically thereafter.
  Bound volumes of The Monitor (1914-70), pamphlets, leaflets, flyers (1958-66, 1976-78), reprints from The Monitor (1963-65), Legislative Brief (1977-79), Bulletin (1978-79), This Week from the Capital (1978-79), Insight, (1979).
  - The Monitor, 1914-1931 (Box 6 (7-Publications of Associated Industries), Folder 1)
  - The Monitor, 1931-1943 (Box 7 (7-Publications of Associated Industries), Folder 1)
  - The Monitor, 1943-1963 (Box 10 (7-Publications of Associated Industries), Folder 1)
  - The Monitor, 1963-1970 (Box 11 (7-Publications of Associated Industries), Folder 1)
  - Bulletin, 1978-1979 (Box 8 (7-Publications of Associated Industries), Folder 1)
  - Insight, 1979 (Box 8 (7-Publications of Associated Industries), Folder 2)
  - Leaflets and Flyers, 1976-1978 (Box 8 (7-Publications of Associated Industries), Folder 3)
  - Legislative Brief, 1977-1979 (Box 8 (7-Publications of Associated Industries), Folder 4)
  - Mapbook of Senate and Assembly Districts, 1966 (Box 8 (7-Publications of Associated Industries), Folder 5)
  - The Monitor, monthly magazine, reprints, 1963-1965 (Box 8 (7-Publications of Associated Industries), Folder 6)
  - Monitor, quarterly leaflet, 1978 (Box 8 (7-Publications of Associated Industries), Folder 7)
  - Pamphlets and Leaflets published by Associated Industries, 1958-1966 (Box 8 (7-Publications of Associated Industries), Folder 8)
  - This Week from the Capital, 1978; 1979 (Box 8 (7-Publications of Associated Industries), Folder 9-10)
- Issues File, 1971-1972; 1977-1979; 8; 0.4 cubic ft.
  Arranged by alphabetically by subject.
  News releases from various sources, news clippings, copies of legislative acts.
  - Action Community for Tax Relief--Now (ACT--NOW), News Clippings, 1979 (Box 8 (8-Issues File), Folder 11)
  - Action Community for Tax Relief--Now (ACT--NOW), Notes and News Releases, 1977-1979 (Box 8 (8-Issues File), Folder 12)
  - Medicaid and Welfare, News Clippings, 1971-1972 (Box 8 (8-Issues File), Folder 13)
  - Social Services, New York State Department of, News Releases and Allied Material, 1971-1972 (Box 8 (8-Issues File), Folder 14-15)
  - Welfare, 1971-1972 (Box 8 (8-Issues File), Folder 16)
  - Welfare, News Clippings, 1971-1972 (Box 8 (8-Issues File), Folder 17)
  - Welfare, News Clippings and Copies of Legislative Acts, 1971-1972 (Box 8 (8-Issues File), Folder 18)
  - Workmen's Compensation, news releases about, 1977 (Box 8 (8-Issues File), Folder 19)
- Legal Counsel Records, Files, 1920; 1945-1947; 1952-1980; 9; 1 cubic foot
  Arranged alphabetically by subject.
  Mostly the papers of different partners of Costello, Cooney ;amp Fearon, counsel for Associated Industries, including legal briefs and pertinent correspondence (1974-80), proposed by-laws (1972, 1976-77), employment file on Raymond T. Schuler (1977-79), certificates of incorporation and of tax exempt status (1920, 1945-47, 1953-56, 1962, 1972), subject files on workmen's compensation, pregnancy disability benefits, social security, unemployment insurance and lobbying (1958-59, 1966-70, 1975-79).
  - Active Industry for the Development of the Economy, Inc. (AIDE), 1976 (Box 8 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 20)
  - By-Laws, Proposed, 1976; 1972; 1976-1978 (Box 8 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 21-22)
  - Environmental Conservation Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 8 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 23)
  - Incorporation Certificates and Tax Exempt Papers, 1920; 1945-1947; 1953-1956; 1962; 1972 (Box 8 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 24)
  - Legal Briefs and Correspondence, includes correspondence on AINY's merger with Empire State Chamber of Commerce, 1974-1980 (Box 8 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 25)
  - Legal Briefs and Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1976; 1976-1979 (Box 8 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 26-27)
  - Lobbying Act, 1977-1979 (Box 8 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 28-29)
  - Lobbying Activities, Earnings of Salaried Employees Attributable to, Report to the Secretary of State, and Relevant Correspondence, 1975 (Box 8 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 30)
  - Meetings of Associated Industries, Papers Concerning, 1975-1978; 1979-1980 (Box 8 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 31-32)
  - New York Telephone vs. the Department of Labor, 1973; 1977 (Box 8 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 33)
  - Opinions on Legislation, 1975 (Box 9 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 1)